# IRFAN NURFATHONI PUTRA



## ABOUT ME

I attended 2 silat martial arts colleges in my junior school and high school, and I also served in the student council at my high school as a member of the spiritual section. Together with members of my group organization, I learned many things, one of which was working together at various events and taking part as a committee member at national events held by my school organization. I am also an expert in serving guests or customers because I have some experience working when I was on holiday in the middle of school

#### EXPERIENCE

March 2017 - August 2017

Employees in a photocopy

March 2022 - March 2023

 Rohis member in the high school student organization

June 2023 - August 2023

Employees at Big Army Store

## CONTACT



0812-3456-7890



hello@irnnft.com



@SADRAH

## EDUCATION

2011 - 2016 Elementary school

2017 - 2019 Junior high school

2020 - 2023 Islamic Boarding school IPA department

2023 - Now Sultan Syarif Kasim State Islamic University of Riau Informatics Engineering

#### FAVORITE

- 1. Listening to music
- 2. Sport
- 3. Watching movies

#### SKILL

- Storytelling
- Discuss
- Public Speaker
- Martial Arts
- Beginner Programming